{
    "response_code": 0,
    "results": [
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "This is the correct spelling of &quot;Supercalifragilisticexpialidocious&quot;.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "In &quot;Portal 2&quot;, Cave Johnson started out Aperture Science as a shower curtain company.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Geography",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "Switzerland has four national languages, English being one of them.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Books",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "Harry Potter was born on July 31st, 1980.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Science & Nature",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "The chemical element Lithium is named after the country of Lithuania.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "Druid is a mage class in &quot;Log Horizon&quot;.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Television",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "The Klingon home planet is Qo&#039;noS.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "The song Scatman&#039;s World was released after Scatman (Ski-Ba-Bop-Ba-Dop-Bop).",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Mythology",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "Janus was the Roman god of doorways and passageways.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "The video game &quot;Fuel&quot; has an open world that is 5,560 square miles?",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        }
    ]
}